Starting from the top, the first element has the attribute class.
بدءًا من البداية، يحتوي العنصر الاول على السمة class.
And it is set to the value, right.
وتم إعدادها على القيمة right.
This matches up with our c.s.s.
وهذا يطابق c.s.s.
So that works.
فهذا يعمل.
The second element also has the attribute class.
يحتوي العنصر الثاني أيضًا على السمة class.
But it is being set to the value leftright.
ولكن تم إعدادها على القيمة leftright.
Although right is part of the entire value leftright, this won't work.
على الرغم من أن right هي جزر من القيمة leftright، لن يعمل هذا.
If we wanted to match on this element, then we would need to change
إذا أردنا التطابق مع هذا العنصر، فسنحتاج
the selector in our CSS to the entire word leftright instead of just right.
لتغيير المحدد في CSS إلى الكلمة الكاملة leftright بدلاً من right فقط.
Our third element has the attribute id and it is being set to the value right.
يحتوي العنصر الثالث على السمة id وتم إعدادها على القيمة right.
This also doesn't work.
لن يعمل هذا أيضًا.
The reason why is because our CSS statement is looking to match
والسبب لأن جملة CSS تريد التطابق مع
on the class right.
class التي على القيمة right.
Not the id right.
وليس id الذي على القيمة right.
Finally, the fourth element has the attribute class, and
أخيرًا، يحتوي العنصر الرابع على السمة class
it is set to three different values.
وتم إعدادها على ثلاث قيم مختلفة.
Highlight, module, and right.
Highlight و module و right.
While this seems like it wouldn't work, it actually does.
بينما يبدو ذلك أنه لا يعمل، فإنه يعمل في الحقيقة.
That's because you can set multiple classes to an element,
وهذا لأنك يمكنك إعداد فئات متعددة لعنصر واحد
as long as they are separated by spaces.
طالما يفصل بينهم مسافات.
Also, the order of the classes doesn't matter.
أيضًا، لا يهم ترتيب الفئات.